New Delhi records wettest July day in decades as deadly floods hit northern India
Six dead after knife attack outside kindergarten in Chinese city
The planet is getting hotter fast. This is what happens to your body in extreme heat
Dutch PM Mark Rutte to leave politics after government collapses
Canadian teenager questioned for allegedly defacing a UNESCO-listed temple in Japan
Teenager Mirra Andreeva produces surprise Wimbledon win
Why Ukraine’s plea for NATO membership is such a profound dilemma for the West
Gym, spa, beauty equipment: Leaked documents reveal hidden details of Putin’s ‘ghost’ train
How Americans can see a rare Northern Lights show this week
BBC suspends presenter following sexual misconduct allegations
Here we go again: Harry Styles hit in eye with object while performing on stage at Vienna concert
China’s factory gate prices fall at fastest pace in 7 years
Mark Zuckerberg concealed his kids’ faces on Instagram. Should you?
In world’s most expensive property market, homes for the dead can cost more than for the living
Bed rotting: TikTok’s latest trend reveals the toxic side of self-care
The huge blob of seaweed headed for Florida has shrunk by 75%
1 dead, 3 injured after gunman fired from scooter in apparent random shooting spree: NYPD
Authorities swoop on Chinese restaurant that challenged customers to eat 108 dumplings
When a tourist in Bali gets arrested, this is the woman they call
A 45-year-old got pregnant in a state with a ban on abortions. She flew across the country to get one
AI-powered humanoid robots field questions from reporters
This is what happens when ChatGPT tries to create crochet patterns
Aerial footage shows scope of massive protests ahead of key vote
Elon Musk is the gift that keeps on giving to Mark Zuckerberg
Netherlands to return nearly 500 looted objects to Indonesia and Sri Lanka
Nudist explains what you should definitely not do at a nude beach
This is the real reason Ron DeSantis is struggling in the polls
River is so polluted that it now has layer of toxic foam
Spider mite males ‘undress’ their partners to mate ASAP
Marble head unearthed during works in Rome piazza
Underarm serve backfires as Spain’s Alejandro Davidovich Fokina loses thrilling five-set match to Holger Rune
How to spice up your pantry the Mediterranean way
Pence, Trump court Iowa voters in hopes of getting early state momentum
‘Tonight is the final night’: Elton John says goodbye to over 50 years of touring with last show on his farewell tour
China fines Jack Ma’s Ant Group nearly $1 billion
The US economy can’t function smoothly without UPS. That’s why a strike will hurt
Some investors are shunning Wall Street’s tech frenzy
China’s export curbs on raw materials are concerning, Yellen says on Beijing trip
One of Philadelphia’s top chefs met her future husband on a plane. Then they traveled the world together
The secret side of Turkey’s Aegean coast
Bedbugs: What travelers need to know this summer
White people meals? The story behind China’s ‘coldest’ food trend
The world’s biggest cruise ship is almost ready
500 days after the invasion of Ukraine, Russian and Belarusian stars are playing at Wimbledon. Here’s how it’s going
Shericka Jackson becomes joint-fifth fastest woman of all time after winning women’s 100m at Jamaican championships
Megan Rapinoe announces she will retire at the end of the season
An emotional Michelle Wie West enjoys magical ending at US Women’s Open on her last competitive appearance
Powerful images from environmental photography prize show challenges and hope
Soccer great Edwin van der Sar in intensive care following bleed around brain, says former club Ajax
Renowned architect Sir David Adjaye steps back from multiple projects amid sexual misconduct allegations
Blue body paint and beaded jeans: The top moments from Paris Haute Couture Week
Gabriela Hearst to step down as creative director of Chloé
The 91-year-old male model with the face of a classic cinema star
Japan’s tallest skyscraper, part of ambitious ‘urban village,’ completed in Tokyo
Putin faces a challenging task that threatens his power
Whatever happened to Mutually Assured Destruction?
Ukrainian writer Victoria Amelina never got to finish her story. We must tell it for her
Trump’s enthusiasm for bringing back Michael Flynn is a revealing sign
Indiana Jones passes his mantle to the queen of millennial side-eye
Why Trump’s Republican rivals should focus on New Hampshire, not Iowa
How Michael Flynn went down the conspiracy theory rabbit hole
Grace Napolitano, longtime California congresswoman, announces her retirement
Federal appeals court allows Tennessee ban on gender-affirming care for transgender minors to take effect
Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez supports Biden’s reelection bid
Ancient shrimplike predator was misunderstood, according to new research
Forget TikTok claims: ‘Nature’s Ozempic’ is no such thing, experts say
Saturn’s rings shine in new Webb telescope photo
Scientists find new clue in what led to megalodon’s demise
Ingenuity helicopter phones home from Mars after 63-day silence
Samsung flags massive drop in quarterly profit as chip glut drags on
Twitter threatens to sue Meta after rival app Threads gains traction
A flying car prototype just got an airworthiness certificate from the FAA
Meta officially launches Twitter rival Threads. 30 million have joined already
With Twitter in chaos, Mark Zuckerberg looks to pounce
Wounded US Army vet Sam Brown targets vulnerable Nevada Democrat with fresh Senate bid: 'Out of touch'
AOC dragged for answer in ‘softball’ MSNBC interview with Jen Psaki: ‘Really pathetic'
Mission: Impossible' star Tom Cruise rules Hollywood, won't bow to ‘woke ideology' experts
Moms for Liberty righteous fire is spreading fast
Stabbing at kindergarten in China leaves 6 dead, continues series of knife attacks in gun-free country
Biden lets American military info slip during live interview, sparking backlash
Trace Gallagher's 'FOX News @ Night' aims to be 'America's late news for entire country' with move to 11 pm ET
Man accused in deadly Fourth of July shooting in Philadelphia may have killed one victim days before holiday
Jonah Hill sells 'complete unrelenting control' merch after being accused of 'emotional abuse' by ex
Dad throws chicken feed at SC school board for being 'too afraid' to take action on explicit library books
Britain gripped with 'a lot of unhappiness' at state of country's politics amid Biden visit
Ray Romano focusing on fun at American Century, shares hilarious story from 2021 tournament
Vermont police officer, 19, killed during high-speed chase involving burglary suspect
Northern Lights expected to be visible in 17 states Thursday
Hard-living Kim Jong Un earns unflattering nickname over massive appetite for European booze, food: expert
50 Cent says Los Angeles is 'finished' after zero bail policy reinstatement: 'Watch how bad it gets'
California homes evacuated, destroyed by landslide in Los Angeles County: officials
Jackie Kennedy learned marijuana was growing on Cape Cod property, fought to keep it quiet: book
Harry Styles hit in the eye by hurled object during concert, in latest incident of recent trend
Dem governor in deep blue state faces chorus of boos at concert as singer tries to hush them up
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez weighs in on GOP primary race, says one candidate made serious 'critical errors'
Former Louisiana Catholic priest pleads guilty to drugging and molesting 17 men, sentenced to prison
More Chinese ditching Xi’s 'Chinese Dream' for an American one
MSNBC panel mocks Casey DeSantis as 'America's Karen,' 'all kinds of names for her'
Flash flooding threat in parts of Northeast could rival rainfall produced by Hurricane Irene in 2011
NYC scooter shooting suspect charged with murder, accused of randomly firing at pedestrians
Maryland State Trooper charged with possessing child pornography
Amsterdam plans 'erotic center' as struggling red light district spirals
Texas man with 'one of the most extensive' child pornography collections sentenced to 30 years in prison
Manhunt for escaped Pennsylvania jail inmate, murder suspect continues
Six people killed in fiery California plane crash identified by Riverside County coroner
‘Messed up': Americans react to Biden’s handling of the economy and ‘Bidenomics’ push
Nurse fired for secret affair with patient who died during sex in hospital parking lot
LSU baseball stars make history at MLB Draft as first two players off the board
Oklahoma judge dismisses lawsuit seeking reparations for 1921 Tulsa Race Massacre
The one key thing my wife taught me to do after her death
Special needs teacher fired after school district discovered OnlyFans account denies 'egregious' conduct
New York City mom stands up to government overreach post-COVID: 'Mom Army is stepping into the breach'
Former Tennessee Sen Roy Herron killed in jet ski crash: ‘Will be missed by us all’
NBC's Chuck Todd accuses GOP of trying to 'exploit' Biden over not acknowledging his 7th grandchild
Elton John delivers final performance on his farewell tour: 'It's been my lifeblood'
Elon Musk ramps up attacks against Zuckerberg with personal insult over Threads app: 'Zuck is a cuck'
Transwoman model wins Miss Universe Netherlands in historic moment: 'I DID IT'
‘Indiana Jones’ loses top box office spot to ‘Insidious’ sequel
Is Walmart stock worth buying?
On this day in history, July 10, 1856, inventor Nikola Tesla is born: 'Keen interest in nature'
McDonald's in India drops tomatoes from burgers, wraps amid shortage
Andrey Rublev hits ridiculous winner, stuns opponent at Wimbledon
As NATO Gathers, Unity Among the Alliance Has Become Harder to Sustain
A Tangled Past Complicates Poland’s Welcome to Ukrainian Refugees
Future of Wagner Leader’s Business Empire Is Cloudy After Rebellion
Do Hormone Treatments for Menopause Increase Dementia Risk?
The Southwest Bakes With More Heat on the Way
The Flawed Moral Logic of Sending Cluster Munitions to Ukraine
Ron DeSantis Doesn’t Know Whether He’s Coming or Going
At Least 1 Dead as Heavy Rains Set Off Flash Flooding in New York
See Pictures of the Flooding in New York
Full Speed Ahead on A.I. Our Economy Needs It.
Look at What John Roberts and His Court Have Wrought Over 18 Years
The Tale of Two Invasions: What the Last Attack on Jenin Tells Us About Israel Now
The Turtle Who Came Back From the Dead
The Next Battle Over Colorblindness Has Begun
For a President and a King, the View From the Top Is Curiously Similar
A NATO Invitation Will Make or Break Ukraine
Who Truly Threatens the Church?
Tuberville Blockade Over Abortion Policy Threatens Top Military Promotions
Why China’s Young People Are Not Getting Married
An Uneasy Quiet at NATO’s Newest Border With Russia
How Mistaken Identity and One Bullet Revealed a Star Predator Far From Home
As Cases Soar, ‘Dementia Villages’ Look Like the Future of Home Care
5 National Park Destinations That Aren’t Parks
OceanGate, Operator of the Titan Submersible, Suspends Operations
It’s Too Hot to Cook. Make These Cool Summer Recipes Instead.
Mark Rutte, Netherlands Prime Minister, Says He Will Leave Politics
At Wimbledon, the Human Eye Keeps Dropping the Ball
Tips for Canceling Online Subscriptions
They Caught the Fish, but the $3.5 Million Prize Got Away
Man Is Charged With Murder in Random Scooter Shooting Spree
Six Dead After Stabbing at a Preschool in China
Yan Mingfu, Who Tried to Defuse the Tiananmen Powder Keg, Dies at 91
Fire on Newark Ship Is Slowly Being Contained, Coast Guard Says
Jack Goldstein, a Savior of Broadway Theaters, Dies at 74
10 Nutrition Myths Experts Wish Would Die
How to Make Travel Easier on Your Body
Feeling Dismissed? How to Spot ‘Medical Gaslighting’ and What to Do About It.
When You Can’t Stand the Sound of Chewing (or Crunching, or Sniffling)
Why Is Pickleball So Popular?
How Beckham’s transformative MLS contract paved the way for Messi
The fall and rise of U.S. tennis. Now they need a grand-slam winner
Northwestern suspends coach Pat Fitzgerald for 2 weeks after investigation into hazing allegations
Megan Rapinoe’s retirement announcement stirs emotions with a World Cup to come
Did that really happen? Barbados v Grenada and a deliberate own goal
Davidovich Fokina loses to Rune after hitting underarm serve at 8-8 in tie-break
We’ve Loved This Summer’s Hottest Sneaker for Years. Here’s Why.
The Best Vanilla Ice Cream
The Best Online Framing Services
The Best Hiking Boots
Kennedy, Christie and the Supreme Court: Are They Changing the Race?
American Cities Have a Conversion Problem, and It’s Not Just Offices
Peter Nero, Pianist Who Straddled Genres, Is Dead at 89
Nikki McCray-Penson, Basketball Star and Coach, Dies at 51
With Supreme Court Decision, College Admissions Could Become More Subjective
With End of Affirmative Action, a Push for a New Tool: Adversity Scores
The ‘Unseen’ Students in the Affirmative Action Debate
Is Aretha Franklin’s True Will the One Found in the Couch or a Cabinet?
On Her Renaissance Tour, the World Is Beyoncé’s Ball
Rare flash flood warning issued for New York as a woman dies trying to evacuate
Biden in Europe live updates: President arrives in U.K. for talks
State laws targeting LGBTQ rights have a new foe: federal judges
NATO summit could test Biden's unity promise
Biden defends 'difficult decision' to give Ukraine cluster bombs amid congressional pushback
Judges in Kentucky and Tennessee block parts of transgender youth care bans
U.S. judge blocks Florida ban on care for trans minors in narrow ruling, says ‘gender identity is real’
1st victim of alleged Philadelphia mass shooter was killed 44 hours earlier, police say
Marine taken into custody after missing 14-year-old girl is found in barracks of California base
These tenants fought one of America's largest corporate landlords — and scored some wins
Police link man to two women whose bodies were found in different Minnesota storage units
Georgia mayor arrested on burglary and trespassing charges
1 dead, at least 15 injured after car driving wrong way collides with bus in Chicago
FDA asked to investigate Logan Paul’s energy drink, PRIME, which has the caffeine of 6 Coke cans
3 Georgia teens charged with murder after plot to egg a home goes wrong, police say
Videos of unconscious boys' rapes found on phone left at restaurant, police say
GOP presidential candidate Doug Burgum says he wouldn't do business with Trump
Dozens of witnesses have testified as the Jan. 6-focused grand jury probes Trump
Ron DeSantis' presidential bid is giving life to a struggling Florida Democratic Party
Biden heads to Europe with a king and a war on his agenda
Aretha Franklin’s sons are going to court over her estate. Here’s what to know.
'Dolores Roach' actor Justina Machado still loves empanadas — though not the horror-filled kind
The internet is obsessed with Taylor Swift's friendship with Taylor Lautner and wife, Tay Lautner
Did 'Barbie' cross the line? How a 'child-like' map stirred a South China Sea dispute
Keke Palmer is the latest Black mother facing backlash over what she wears
Why this summer's big sporting events might look a little different
Is Russia purging Wagner Group troops in Africa?
6 are killed in stabbing at kindergarten in China
U.S. drone strike kills an Islamic State group leader in Syria, the Defense Department says
Britain's BBC faces questions as presenter is accused of paying teenager for pictures
The 7 best e-readers of 2023, according to experts
Select Best for Your Pet Awards 2023: Reader favorites
The best garden hoses, nozzles and reels to shop in 2023, according to experts
Target Circle Week: Who has access, when deals are available and more
U.S. women’s soccer star Megan Rapinoe announces retirement
Chicago couple creates gardens and jobs for at-risk youth
Man who lost job becomes bestselling author after viral video
Video shows crash site of small plane that killed six in California field
12 homes evacuated in Rolling Hills Estates after ground shifts
High-stakes, high-stress college essay stirs more anxiety under affirmative action ban
The Californians whose scam PACs tricked Trump and Clinton supporters out of millions
How second-generation owners of 99 Ranch are turning the Asian supermarket into a national powerhouse
Victims in fatal Riverside County plane crash identified
The Dodgers are favorites to sign Shohei Ohtani. Will the third time be the charm?
Listen up, lavender lovers: The Lavender Festival is in full bloom
How to have the best Sunday in L.A., according to Kiersey Clemons
Questions about age trail Rep. Barbara Lee, 76, as she seeks Sen. Dianne Feinstein’s seat
Huntington Beach lifeguard, a former water polo standout, suffers spinal injury on duty
Dodgers option slumping rookie Miguel Vargas. So who plays second base now?
Girl found in Camp Pendleton barracks was raped by Marine, family alleges
16 favorite places to slurp down oysters in L.A. this summer
The lasting threat is not the ‘next Trump,’ but the MAGA base
Mexican Mafia member who ran county jail rackets is killed in prison
What if abortion was self-defense?
 Reeling Angels need to swallow hard and trade Shohei Ohtani
Dead Beatles, Fake Drake and robot songwriters: Inside the panic over AI music
Michelin or World’s 50 Best Restaurants: Which is more relevant?
Go inside the Museum of Neon Art’s storage facility for a rare glimpse of vivid treasures
Six people killed in plane crash near Riverside County airport
The U.S. labor market is starting to show cracks. Here are the signs
Inspired at the Getty, L.A. teen’s duct tape dress among scholarship contest’s finalist
Ukraine and expansion top NATO agenda as Biden tries to cement unity
The Sports Report: Dodgers send Miguel Vargas to the minors
Here’s how small California businesses can compete for big government contracts
9th Circuit conservatives blast homelessness ruling, say issue is ‘paralyzing’ U.S. West
High-stakes, high-stress college essay stirs more anxiety under affirmative action ban
Immigrant women are joining the job market at record levels, boosting U.S. employment
A user’s guide to Taylor Swift’s ‘Speak Now (Taylor’s Version)’
The Hollywood Bowl opens with Dudamel and raft of favorites
‘Insidious: The Red Door’ takes on ‘Indiana Jones’ at the box office
‘Insidious 5’ topples ‘Indiana Jones’ before ‘Mission: Impossible’ launches
Peter Nero, Grammy-winning pianist and Philly Pops conductor, dies at 89
For Trump, the 2024 election looks like 2016 with who is running for president. Here are key differences
Putin and Wagner leader Prigozhin met in Moscow five days after failed rebellion
Four stats from a Supreme Court term that gutted affirmative action, student debt relief
'Everyone is burnt out': Why chefs and restaurateurs are leaving the industry in droves
Hayley Atwell addresses 'invasive' Tom Cruise dating rumors: 'It feels a little dirty'
MLB draft takeaways: Pirates' urgency, SEC dominance and two-way star finds good home
Is Diet Coke worse for you than regular? The answer may surprise you.
"East Coast flash flooding leaves 1 person dead; triple-digit heat in Southwest: Monday weather"
Biden trumpets 'rock solid' U.K. relationship ahead of King Charles meeting
Judge dismisses 1921 Tulsa Race Massacre lawsuit seeking restitution
Honda, Mercedes-Benz among 133,000 recalled vehicles. Check car recalls here.
Margot Robbie, Ryan Gosling, Dua Lipa, more stars hit pink carpet at 'Barbie' premiere
Many say to set your AC to 78 in the summer to save money. But should you?
Chris Christie says he has doubts over Hunter Biden investigation: Either 'a lie' or 'incompetent'
Former President Barack Obama asks to play round with US Women's Open champ Allisen Corpuz
How Biden might Try to Cancel Student Debt Next
Schumer calls for FDA probe into caffeine content of PRIME energy drinks
'We are putting an end to this': Israel's raid on Palestinian Jenin camp stretches into 2nd day
War would end within days if West stopped arming Ukraine, Russia says: Live updates
The oceans are unusually hot and on track to get hotter. That's not good.
NASCAR Atlanta summer 2023 race: Start time, TV, streaming, lineup for Quaker State 400
Bruce Springsteen wows the faithful at London's Hyde Park: 'Do you wanna go home? I don't'
"Two Minnesota missing women found dead in storage units; police link both to the same man"
19-year-old arrested after 2 dead, 4 injured in Bay St. Louis, Mississippi, house party shooting
Ukraine hits Crimea depot as nation gears up for spring offensive: Updates
RNC chair Ronna McDaniel: GOP candidates have to address abortion 'head on'
House GOP Whip Tom Emmer declines to outright guarantee U.S. will not default on its debts
California man known as 'City of Hope patient' comes forward, 1 of 5 cured of HIV worldwide
2023 USA track and field championships winners and losers
Ukraine tops NATO summit agenda along with defense plans, Sweden's membership and Belarus fears
Islamic State leader killed while on motorcycle by US drones Russia had 'harassed': Officials
Man with knife kills 6 people at kindergarten in China before being arrested, police and reports say
Heavy rains cause flooding and mudslides in southwest Japan, leaving 2 dead and at least 6 missing
Phoenix to show compliance with court order to clear 'The Zone' homeless encampment
12 homes evacuated in Southern California city after ground shifts
Las Vegas police officer set to go on trial over $165k stolen in 3 casino heists
New York state flooding updates: 'Complete chaos' overnight as water receded, county exec says
UK police say a second 8-year-old girl has died after an SUV crashed into a Wimbledon school
Gunman at large after shooting 9 people in Cleveland's historic Warehouse District
Northwestern will gather more information on football hazing allegations amid Fitzgerald suspension
Uvalde-area Democrat enters race to unseat Ted Cruz
Accused Philadelphia shooter may have begun his spree nearly two days earlier than police thought
The FDA is being asked to look into Logan Paul's energy drink, which has the caffeine of 6 Coke cans
Simultaneous searches unfolding on opposite sides of the country for suspected murderers who escaped from custody
Zelenskyy to ABC: How Russia-Ukraine war could end, thoughts on US politics and Putin's weakness
 How many Russians have died in Ukraine? Data shows what Moscow hides
US sending controversial cluster munitions to Ukraine until other ammo is ready: Kirby
Biden journeys through Europe ahead of NATO summit